<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Changing Workplace</title>
    <description>The Changing Workplace | We are an industry-leading provider of web-based CAFM software solutions for Corporate Real Estate and Facilities groups.</description>
    <link>http://changingworkplace.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://changingworkplace.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 09:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 09:13:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>We&#39;re Recruiting</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are currently recruiting for a Marketing/Business Development Executive. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The person we want should be calm under pressure and be able to juggle &amp;amp; prioritise their workload, be personable and confident, and not be afraid of being thrown in the deep end and working with some very unique personalities! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read the job description for full details.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://changingworkplace.com/news/job/jobs-5</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changingworkplace.com/news/job/jobs-5</guid>
        
        <category>News</category>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
        <category>job</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vote for us to win!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It gives us great pleasure to announce that our Workplace Tracking - Footfall Monitoring product has been shortlisted for the prestigious Tomorrow’s FM Awards 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now in their third year, the Tomorrow’s FM Awards shine a spotlight on the year’s most impressive and innovative developments in the field of Facilities Management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being shortlisted is a great achievement which we’re delighted by, but we’d be even more thrilled to win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can vote for us by clicking &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.surveymonkey.com/s/fmawards15&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and selecting ‘Footfall Monitoring - The Changing Workplace’ half way down the left hand column.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a strong field once again, and we’re very proud to be shortlisted for this recognition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/tomorrowsfm.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://changingworkplace.com/news/awards-shortlist</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changingworkplace.com/news/awards-shortlist</guid>
        
        <category>News</category>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We&#39;re Recruiting</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are currently recruiting for a motivated and experienced person whose main purpose is to deliver Space Planning/CAFM services to our customer. You will report to the Senior Team Lead and will also be collaborating with other CAFM co-ordinators, the IT Team &amp;amp; various project managers. Read the job description for full details.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://changingworkplace.com/news/job/jobs-1</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changingworkplace.com/news/job/jobs-1</guid>
        
        <category>News</category>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
        <category>job</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Space Management</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Your PDF has been downloaded.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://changingworkplace.com/factsheet/resources/space-management</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changingworkplace.com/factsheet/resources/space-management</guid>
        
        
        <category>factsheet</category>
        
        <category>resources</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Move Manager</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Your PDF has been downloaded.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://changingworkplace.com/factsheet/resources/move-manager</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changingworkplace.com/factsheet/resources/move-manager</guid>
        
        
        <category>factsheet</category>
        
        <category>resources</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MobileCoRE Space Utilisation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;CASE STUDY – (Education Sector client)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirement: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our client is working with a leading University in the north of England who require annual space utilisation surveys. These feed into the information
provided to the Higher Education Statistics Agency (HESA) as part of the Estates Management Record. A big focus was on utilisation to see which rooms were
actually being used once they had been booked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Facilities stats:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surveys took place over a one week period and covered 6 campuses, 29 buildings, 16 floors, 388 rooms and 12,970 workstations over an area of 1M+ sq ft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key drivers:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Streamlining the survey process and meeting HESA legal requirements&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reporting was crucial – the ability to turn data into actionable information&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Empowering staff to make strategic decisions, concentrating on core activity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Implementation:  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After initial meetings and scoping to define requirements and timescales, the MobileCoRE ‘Surveys on the move’ app was populated with the utilisation
survey data ready for simple reporting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Benefits:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Optimum space usage and allocation identified&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;HESA data extracted and available for submission&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Time/money savings and reduced carbon footprint&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reporting influences current provision and future planning&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Evidence-driven analysis and understanding of estate performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Results: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;h5&gt;&lt;i&gt;“MobileCoRE is the perfect app for undertaking space utilisation surveys. It enables consistency, compliance and cost savings for the client. What I
        have also been impressed with is its straight forward set up and the highly visualised reporting metrics that are produced.&quot;
        &lt;br /&gt;
		&lt;br /&gt;
        &quot;It provides the opportunity for evaluation and review by identifying areas for change and further opportunities, either in a University or in any
        public sector or corporate environment. You don’t just get the data, you get a full service with initiation, planning, implementation, analysis and
        review.”&lt;/i&gt;
	&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://changingworkplace.com/casestudy/resources/mobilecore-space-utilisation</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changingworkplace.com/casestudy/resources/mobilecore-space-utilisation</guid>
        
        
        <category>casestudy</category>
        
        <category>resources</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mobile Surveys PPT</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mobile surveys and workplace tracking&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our CEO Steve Thorley gave a presentation at the CoreNet Global APAC Summit in Singapore on the topic of ‘Taking the lead with mobile surveys and workplace tracking’. His presentation was extremely well received and featured on the Summit’s post event blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key takeaways for the presentation were: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Identify ways to utilise new, innovative technology and empower your employees, making them more mobile,
agile and productive &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discover how mobile space surveys and workplace tracking technology can reduce your organisation’s carbon
footprint, drive strategy, add value, increase ROI and create proof points &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Understand the benefits of tracking how the workplace (space) is working at any point in time &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download the full presentation using the icon on the right of the screen.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://changingworkplace.com/whitepaper/resources/mobile-surveys-ppt</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changingworkplace.com/whitepaper/resources/mobile-surveys-ppt</guid>
        
        
        <category>whitepaper</category>
        
        <category>resources</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Workplace Tracking</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Discover your true space utilisation and occupancy potential and answer the three big questions with workplace tracking – footfall monitoring sensor technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;
1. Do we have enough space?&lt;br /&gt; 
2. Do we have too much space? &lt;br /&gt;
3. Can we reconfigure to meet demand? &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Footfall monitoring is about tracking how your workspace is operating and being utilised at any point of time, identifying opportunities so that they can be acted upon and maximising the efficiency and effectiveness of an existing floor or building. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is an ideal solution for corporate real estate professionals to employ on any floor or workspace and can be a precursor to moving to an agile environment by verifying how your portfolio’s current design and layout is working. Uncover crucial data, gain value and make significant cost savings for your organisation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download the full white paper using the icon on the right of the screen.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://changingworkplace.com/whitepaper/resources/workplace-tracking</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changingworkplace.com/whitepaper/resources/workplace-tracking</guid>
        
        
        <category>whitepaper</category>
        
        <category>resources</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WebCoRE</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;WebCoRE is a web-based CAFM system with a suite of modules that help corporate real estate teams manage and report on their portfolios.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hosted on a fully resilient and secure infrastructure, clients have the option of hosting on a shared cloud, or for even more security a dedicated private cloud. Access to the system can be secured further using a VPN connection allowing access only from your corporate network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A ‘Software as a Service’ solution with cloud computing as the infrastructure technology is the way forward for modern, lean-led companies. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download the full white paper using the icon on the right of the screen.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://changingworkplace.com/whitepaper/resources/webcore</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changingworkplace.com/whitepaper/resources/webcore</guid>
        
        
        <category>whitepaper</category>
        
        <category>resources</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reporting Suite</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Your PDF has been downloaded.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://changingworkplace.com/factsheet/resources/reporting-suite</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://changingworkplace.com/factsheet/resources/reporting-suite</guid>
        
        
        <category>factsheet</category>
        
        <category>resources</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
